what is up everyone my name would be
Josh this is strain Central and today we
are going to be doing a product review
on the source orb 3 by source vapes.com
so Source vapes.com sent me over the
source orb 3 XL travel kit along with
the uh Source orb slim travel kit so
this right here is the source orb 3 you
see it has like a little bit of a dome
shape and then this one right here is
the source orb slim it's not that much
Slimmer but it does resemble a little
bit more of like an E6
uh we do have some close-ups of these
kits really quickly so let's go ahead
and get into them so first we're going
to be opening this XL travel kit as you
open it up there's two cloths here for
keeping your Source Faith nice and shiny
and fingerprint free in the back here we
do have the 2600 ma variable voltage
battery let's go ahead and get a closeup
on this variable voltage here you do see
at the highest temperature it does offer
a 4.8 and you can go down pretty much by
the 0.1 all the way down to 3. too going
back to the kit we have a USB charger
and a Dabber that literally every single
vaporizer kit comes with and then there
is the state-of-the-art double quartz
coils which you can see at the end of
this video moving on to the source orbs
Slim So to use this you basically just
pop the top off and grab yourself a
quartz coil you screw the quartz coil
directly onto this connector right here
and then slide the lid right over top
and you are ready to start vaping I was
having a really hard time getting
close-up shots because I was really
caffeinated but this is the adjustable
air flow on the source orb slim so now
we're moving on to the source orb 3 so
it is teardrop shaped or Dome shaped but
it is extremely extremely easy to use
just like the slim you basically just
plug your coil in here and then screw
the top in and you start vaping this is
the slim travel kit so this does not
have anything you didn't see in the
first kit but it's just a little bit
more basic a little bit less expensive
up top we do have the variable voltage
2600 ma battery and then we have the
source orb slim along with your USB
charger and two quartz coils and they do
throw in that basic uh Dabber here so
the reason they call these travel cases
is because they're hard protective cases
that are just about the size of an
iPhone 5S so they fit into your pocket
perfectly and they'll keep your Vape
protected I absolutely love this idea
all right guys so let's go ahead and get
into using these we are going to be
using the source orb 3 first so uh when
it comes to powering these on power them
on like pretty much any other EIG or any
other uh like vaporizer five clicks to
the power button 1 2 3 4 5 and the light
will start blinking and then once the
light starts blinking you are ready to
vape so I definitely hope you guys are
smoking along dabbing along vaping along
getting those C nice and deep into your
lungs because I'm going to get some more
of this CBD oil into mine so cheers guys
go ahead and let the button just for a
couple seconds then they start pulling
slowly slow long draws on
[Music]
these let's get one more
so so
flavorful definitely gives you some
really nice lung
expansion and honestly
emulat emulates a rig really really well
and I think the reason that they emulate
rigs so well is simply because it does
have the double quartz coil
atomizers uh I will put it at the end of
this video up in the eye in the sky a
link to the quartz coil atomizer so you
can see a little more in- depth what
they look like but rather than using
like the normal ceramic or cotton wick
or silica Wick uh they basically just
took two pieces of quartz wrapped the
coils around the quartz and then uh
that's what they put in actually double
coils so it's not one single coil it's
two coils the reason they did this is is
simply to provide a little bit better
flavor a lot of these ceramic Wicks uh
just kind of give off what I would
describe as a burnt taste especially
when you dry fire the Wicks um when it
comes to these even when you dry fire
them or there's not a lot of wax in them
they're still going to give you the true
flavor of the wax uh it's just really
really nice to get the full flavor of
your wax if you're spending money on you
know expensive wax chirpy wax so flavor
game is on point uh your first couple
clouds with these will most of the time
be really big thick milky clouds and
then you'll start getting a little bit
more of like the EIG Vapor but you'll
get some really nice big hits that
really really really closely emulate a
rig and I really really enjoy that this
does have a little bit of like a dome uh
look to it a lot of these eigs have what
people call Globes and they're just like
clear little domes that smoke can stack
up in but if you're using those out in
public and people don't know what they
are it it kind of resembles like a hard
drug use or it just looks sketchy so the
fact that you can't really see the smoke
building up in here is probably a good
thing simply because it makes a little
more stealthy and makes a little more
like on the down low we're going to go
ahead and get a rip off of this uh
Source orb slim though guys so cheers
let's see what this one does
[Music]
I have this one turned
up just a little bit higher uh they are
variable voltage they vary
between cough my lungs out uh they vary
between 3.2 volts and 4.8 volts and I
believe you can pretty much get it by
the voltage uh depending on what you
want it to be so I like that it's
adjustable and you can kind of decide if
you want 4.8 for a little more of a
thick milky Cloud 3.2 for a little bit
less of a Milky cloud and a lot more
flavor but uh going back to the coils
another thing they did do with these is
on majority of eigs or anything that
uses coils uh the temperature range that
they Vape at is really high we're
talking anywhere from about 1,000°
upwards of
1,200 so they're they're well over
1,000° and and that's that's really
really hot to be vaporizing uh your wax
so majority of these wax pens are
actually combustion pens that are just
vaporizing your wax at at these absurd
temper
temperatures these guys drop that
temperature down uh just because they
are using the double coils so I believe
they operate anywhere from about 650 to
about
750° which is almost half the
temperature that your normal EAS egg
will be running at which means that it's
not going to combust your wax like a
majority of these other vaporizers
you're actually going to be getting
vapor from your wax so that's the main
reason why you're going to be getting so
much better flavor from these aside from
the quartz uh it's simple temperature
that they're not going to be combusting
your wax these are true wax
vaporizers as you guys probably saw in
the closeups when you are using the uh
Source orbs slim it does have this
little like completely variable air flow
that kind of allows you to either make
it more drag or less drag uh the source
orb 3 just has basic holes so this thing
it's really really easy to pull
through uh not a lot of effort to
actually pull through this but if you
want this to be a little bit harder to
pull through you can adjust it so you
either get like you know maybe one one
hole of air flow and it's a little bit
harder for you to drag through I I can't
think of a situation where you would
want it to be a little bit harder to
pull through but you know different fol
for different wait Different Strokes for
different I almost said different folks
for Different Strokes I I don't know my
sayings but you guys already know that
uh cons uh I'm going to have to say the
biggest con I do have to say about these
pins is the simple fact that you cannot
use them when they're charging so when
you go to charge them you have to put
them on the USB like this right here and
if you only do have one of them uh it's
going to be in in inac capitated I think
that's the I'm just [\h__\h] up all kinds
of things here it's not going to be able
to be in use is is what I'm trying to
say uh once you plug it in you're going
to have to like leave it plugged in
until the battery's charged so there is
going to be those mornings that you know
you wake up you forgot to throw your
battery on the charger and all of a
sudden you can't use the vaporizer for
the day so that's going to be a big con
for this and then the other con I have
is a relatively small one it's just the
simple fact that they do use threading
I am not a huge fan of this like
threading uh I think that's just because
the g420 C kind of spoiled me but when
it comes to these threadings uh once you
kind of get them waxy and coated in wax
when it comes to screwing them and
unscrewing them it's really hard to do
um I don't think this is 510 threading I
think this is just a little bit bigger
than 510 threading so it is probably
going to be a little bit easier to
unscrew but I have to say those are the
two cons overall though I honestly
absolutely love this thing flavor like
Wax like flavor and Vapor production are
the two things that I'm going to give it
huge points for one of the most
flavorful pens that I have found to use
and also one of the biggest clouds that
I've been able to blow from a pen uh I'm
going to say the overall rating this
gets is a 5.9 out of 7even definitely an
awesome awesome pen but I'm going to go
ahead and rip this one more time and get
out of here I definitely hope you guys
enjoyed this quick review on the source
orb 3 and I hope you guys are having
yourself an absolutely incredible day
please live today with the smile on your
face and actively try to make someone
else's day better if you try to make
other people's life around you better
they're in turn going to make your life
better and it's going to make you feel
better and just the the world will be a
better place we need to stop being so
selfish and actively being like me me me
me me me do something nice for others do
something good for others and in turn
it's going to make you feel better and
it's going to make the world a happier
better place uh I know that's a little
preachy but I always like to add some
kind of encouragement to the end of
these so we're going to go ahead and rip
these and get out of here cheers guys
let's get it
[Music]
stay positive stay medicated peace guys